hey y'all i'm back with another product
review for all the fine and frugal
ladies out there
today i'm trying these salon acrylic
natural nails
that can be worn natural or polished
now honey these might be my new favorite
they're way thicker than all the other
presto nails that i've tried
um i mean there is no bending these at
all
no chipping these i love them
here i tried to show you their thickness
it's not excessively thick but you know
they're definitely thicker than
other press-ons i could definitely see
myself
doing my own little thing with these
adding my own little flavor and sauce
and style and all of that
so you know i'll be back with some diy
nail designs
[Music]
you